[{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664047021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":11424,"timeElapsed":76538},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664057357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":10335,"timeElapsed":86873},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664070692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":13334,"timeElapsed":100209},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664082756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":12063,"timeElapsed":112273},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664091596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":8839,"timeElapsed":121113},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664099268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":7671,"timeElapsed":128785},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664105804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6535,"timeElapsed":135321},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664134892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":29086,"timeElapsed":164409},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664138940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4047,"timeElapsed":168457},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664175084,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":15855,"timeElapsed":204601},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664184204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":9119,"timeElapsed":213721},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664190692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6486,"timeElapsed":220209},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664193236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2543,"timeElapsed":222753},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664196876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3639,"timeElapsed":226393},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664200556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3679,"timeElapsed":230073},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664202948,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":232465},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664211548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":8599,"timeElapsed":241065},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664214060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2511,"timeElapsed":243577},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664223724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8343,"timeElapsed":253241},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664226652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2927,"timeElapsed":256169},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664229828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3174,"timeElapsed":259345},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664232116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2287,"timeElapsed":261633},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664234748,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2631,"timeElapsed":264265},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664240908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":6159,"timeElapsed":270425},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664245108,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4198,"timeElapsed":274625},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664250196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":5087,"timeElapsed":279713},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664252732,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2535,"timeElapsed":282249},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664262036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":7822,"timeElapsed":291553},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664264908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2871,"timeElapsed":294425},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664270084,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5175,"timeElapsed":299601},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664271996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1911,"timeElapsed":301513},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664274372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2375,"timeElapsed":303889},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664277484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3111,"timeElapsed":307001},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664280036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2551,"timeElapsed":309553},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664283068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3031,"timeElapsed":312585},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664285020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1950,"timeElapsed":314537},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664294508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":8343,"timeElapsed":324025},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664299332,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4823,"timeElapsed":328849},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664305324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":5991,"timeElapsed":334841},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664309356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4031,"timeElapsed":338873},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664311485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2127,"timeElapsed":341001},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664315532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":4047,"timeElapsed":345049},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664319285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3751,"timeElapsed":348802},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664321956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2670,"timeElapsed":351473},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664325501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3543,"timeElapsed":355018},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664327404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1902,"timeElapsed":356921},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664336212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":7567,"timeElapsed":365729},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664338556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2343,"timeElapsed":368073},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664342188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3631,"timeElapsed":371705},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664345188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2999,"timeElapsed":374705},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664348636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3446,"timeElapsed":378153},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664351364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2727,"timeElapsed":380881},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664353812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2447,"timeElapsed":383329},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664358612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4799,"timeElapsed":388129},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664360396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1783,"timeElapsed":389913},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664368348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6759,"timeElapsed":397865},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664370076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1727,"timeElapsed":399593},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664372556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2479,"timeElapsed":402073},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664374268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1710,"timeElapsed":403785},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664378932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4663,"timeElapsed":408449},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664384284,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5351,"timeElapsed":413801},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664387860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3574,"timeElapsed":417377},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664390189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2327,"timeElapsed":419705},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664391916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1727,"timeElapsed":421433},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664398380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5383,"timeElapsed":427897},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664401092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2711,"timeElapsed":430609},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664403132,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2039,"timeElapsed":432649},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664406668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3535,"timeElapsed":436185},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664409892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3223,"timeElapsed":439409},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664413092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3199,"timeElapsed":442609},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664415180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2087,"timeElapsed":444697},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664417052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1871,"timeElapsed":446569},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664419028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1975,"timeElapsed":448545},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664426508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6607,"timeElapsed":456025},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664428268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1758,"timeElapsed":457785},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664430709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2439,"timeElapsed":460226},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664432364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1654,"timeElapsed":461881},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664438500,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6135,"timeElapsed":468017},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664440541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2039,"timeElapsed":470058},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664442412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1870,"timeElapsed":471929},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664445229,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2815,"timeElapsed":474745},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664446860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1631,"timeElapsed":476377},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664448412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1551,"timeElapsed":477929},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664456500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6991,"timeElapsed":486017},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664458116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1615,"timeElapsed":487633},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664459893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1775,"timeElapsed":489410},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664462036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2143,"timeElapsed":491553},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664464861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2823,"timeElapsed":494377},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664467652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2791,"timeElapsed":497169},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664470068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2415,"timeElapsed":499585},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664472429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2359,"timeElapsed":501946},{"subjectID":"23a9xg3423","prolificID":"6730b698c72b925f14c5ad40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421572faa64fd6788641f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664474020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1591,"timeElapsed":503537}]